tourcms.com 2009-12-28

# Travel UCD privacy policy

[home](http://www.tourcms.com/) > [company](http://www.tourcms.com/company/) > privacy policy

The _www.TourCMS.com_ website provides online information about the TourCMS service. TourCMS is owned and operated by Travel UCD Limited, UK. 

Travel UCD takes the privacy of our customers' data very seriously. Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal data. 

We use the information provide to the transaction, fulfill your order and provide you with the services you expect. This information may include but is not limited to details such as your name, address and credit card details. 

Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose your personal data to third parties if this is required for the purpose of completing your transaction with us. This is of course subject to the provision that we may disclose your data to certain permitted third parties, such as assigned mentors, affiliated companies or our own professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, and when we are legally obliged to disclose your data. 

We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express content. 

For any of the above purposes we may send your information internationally including to countries outside the EEA. Some of these jurisdictions offer differing levels of protection of personal information, not all of which may be as high as the UK. 

We reserve the right to use the names of TourCMS powered websites (or backend reservation systems) within client portfolios. See Terms of Service for details. 

**Consent**  
By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Travel UCD in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. 

**TourCMS platform**  
If you provide us with information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them, to consent to the processing of their personal data including sensitive personal data and that you have informed them of our identity and the purposes for which their personal data will be processed.
